(Howard:)...to almost do what I almost did.
(Sheldon:)Ah, much better.
(Leonard:)You must be burning up.
(Sheldon:)A little. But not more
than your urethras will be...
(Sheldon:)...after whatever's in those pants
swims up them.
(Sheldon:)Well, I cut quite the dashing
yet hygienic figure, don't l?
l look like the Flash
about to get married.
Oh, a tissue! A tissue! Oh, good Lord!
(Assistant:)Uh, where's he going?
(Leonard:)He keeps emergency Purell
in the car.
Keys. Keys. Keys.
(Penny:)- Hey, you.
- Before I come in, you should know...
...l have gas.
(Penny:)For the record,
not your worst opening line.
(Leonard:)Check it out. It's the gas I use
in my laser to support high voItages.
(Leonard:)But it also has an interesting
secondary use.